

Fio Auer

Creative Frontend Developer (they/them)

fio2auer5@gmail.com

+49 152 19731987



Berlin, Germany



figauer.com

5+ years of experience in the Tech industry. Passionate about building products that matter. Experienced and skilled with the stack of React, Next.js, Typescript, REST API and GraphQL as well as using Contentful as CMS. I've also passionate about designing websites from scratch.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Creative Frontend Developer Freelancer Self-employed &

09/2023 - 11/2024

- Achieved results/Tasks
- Web flow development
- Typescript, Node, Vue.js, React, Next.js
- Conceptualization, Design, SEO help and Product Management

Frontend Developer

01/2022 - 07/2023

Copenhagen, Denmark

Achievements/Tasks

- Taking lead on building the Frontend of The Org revenue product: https://vision.theorg.com/
- Maintaining & optimizing existing code base of both The Org and Vision
- SEO and tracking optimizations for The Org core product

Product Manager GOODIEBOX ♂

09/2020 - 08/2021

Copenhagen, Denmark

- Achievements/Tasks
- Task scoping, product research & customer insight analysis.
- Internal process optimization by building efficient tools.
- Product managing a new Frontpage and signup flow implementation.

Junior Product Owner (Part-Time)

Omnio.net 🗷

10/2019 - 06/2020

Copenhagen, Denmark

- Achievements/Tasks
- Adopting agile management and processes.
- Support managing the backlog and sprints of all teams.
- Managing the certification for security in IoT.

EDUCATION

M.Sc. BA & Information Systems - Ebuss

Copenhagen Business School (CBS) &

09/2018 - 06/2020

Copenhagen, Denmark

Guest Student - Computer Science

IT University of Copenhagen &

09/2019 - 01/2020

Copenhagen, Denmark

B.Sc. Management & Technology

Technical University of Munich

10/2013 - 09/2017

Munich, Germany

Exchange Semester

01/2016 - 05/2016

Helsinki. Finland

SKILLS

React	• • • • •
Next.js	
Typescript	• • • • •
Vue.js	
Nuxt.js	
Figma	
Contentful	

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer & Team Lead at Bank.Green (10/2023 - 11/2024)

Developing on the website and a Green Policy Evaluator in Vue.js, Nuxt.js and REST API

Global Head of Journey at TechLabs (09/2021 - 09/2022)

Leading the Global Journey Team responsible for holistically & strategically designing the core TL product for all 16 locations.

Head of Journey & Co-Founder at TechLabs Copenhagen (03/2019 - 06/2020) 🗗

We build a community to dive into AI, Data Science, and Web Development, for anyone with and without any previous programming knowledae.

Head of Communication & Co-Founder at CBS IT Union (06/2019 - 02/2020)

Starting up a Union for all IT Masters at CBS

LANGUAGES

English (C2) German (native)

INTERESTS

